[{"answer": " Its on Gavin.  American Idol is starting", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Here I am.  I love this show.  I cant wait to see who gets voted off this week", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Its on Gavin.  American Idol is starting", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I think it might be Kelly.  She didnt sing very well last week", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Here I am.  I love this show.  I cant wait to see who gets voted off this week", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": "It could be her, or it could be Rubin.  He was in the bottom three contestant", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " I think it might be Kelly.  She didnt sing very well last week", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well see tonight.  Im so excited.  What do you think will. HEY!  What wa", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 17, "question": "It could be her, or it could be Rubin.  He was in the bottom three contestant", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " It must be the storm outside.  Maybe lightning hit the house", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Well see tonight.  Im so excited.  What do you think will. HEY!  What wa", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Look at the TV.  Its all blank.  Our show is gone!  No!!!!!!", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " It must be the storm outside.  Maybe lightning hit the house", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Oh no!  Now what are we going to do", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Look at the TV.  Its all blank.  Our show is gone!  No!!!!!!", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Should we wait and see what happens or call the cable company", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Oh no!  Now what are we going to do", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " I think you should call the cable company", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Should we wait and see what happens or call the cable company", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " OK.  Let me get their number", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 31, "question": " I think you should call the cable company", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Charter Cable, can I help you", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " OK.  Let me get their number", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yes, hi.  We have an emergency.  Our TV went out in the middle of our favorit", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Charter Cable, can I help you", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Im sorry to hear that, maam.  Can I have your name and accoun", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Yes, hi.  We have an emergency.  Our TV went out in the middle of our favorit", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Yes, Its Gwen Stepania and my account number is 85-256-4452", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Im sorry to hear that, maam.  Can I have your name and accoun", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Can you please give me the last four digits of your social securit", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Yes, Its Gwen Stepania and my account number is 85-256-4452", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Yes, its 0253", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Can you please give me the last four digits of your social securit", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK, our system is showing that there are strong thunderstorms in you", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Yes, its 0253", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Yes.  We heard a large bang", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 55, "question": " OK, our system is showing that there are strong thunderstorms in you", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Oh, thats not good.  Your TV could have been struck by lightning.  I", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Yes.  We heard a large bang", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Yeah, its on, but the screen is just all blank", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Oh, thats not good.  Your TV could have been struck by lightning.  I", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " OK, please turn the TV off until one of our technicians can come ou", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Yeah, its on, but the screen is just all blank", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Can someone come right now to fix it", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 65, "question": " OK, please turn the TV off until one of our technicians can come ou", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I dont think so maam.  Let me check our computer systems for th", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Can someone come right now to fix it", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " What?  Thats four days from now", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 71, "question": " I dont think so maam.  Let me check our computer systems for th", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Im sorry.  That is the earliest available time", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " What?  Thats four days from now", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " All right.  I can be here Tuesday morning.  What time", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Im sorry.  That is the earliest available time", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " A technician will be there sometime between 8:00am and 12:00 noon", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " All right.  I can be here Tuesday morning.  What time", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Can we set up a specific time", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 78, "question": " A technician will be there sometime between 8:00am and 12:00 noon", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " No maam.  You just have to be there from 8:00 to 12:00 and theyl", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Can we set up a specific time", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 83, "question": " No maam.  You just have to be there from 8:00 to 12:00 and theyl", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Can you please confirm your address and phone number for me", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Its 256 Highland Avenue, Hollywood, California 78520.  My number is 844-966", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Can you please confirm your address and phone number for me", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " OK, well send someone out on Tuesday morning.  Is there anythin", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Its 256 Highland Avenue, Hollywood, California 78520.  My number is 844-966", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " No, thank you", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 93, "question": " OK, well send someone out on Tuesday morning.  Is there anythin", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Good-bye", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " No, thank you", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Well, what did they say?  Are they coming to fix it", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Good-bye", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " No, not until next Tuesday.  Now we cant watch American Idol", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Well, what did they say?  Are they coming to fix it", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Lets go to Justins house to watch it", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " No, not until next Tuesday.  Now we cant watch American Idol", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " OK  lets go", "docId": "11-01", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Lets go to Justins house to watch it", "qSentId": 100}]
